WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
Ton', will you
get that?
Hello?
Tony, it's me.
Don't hang up.
The fuck are you
calling here for,
you know who could
answer this phone?
Please, you are
so conceited.
Do you really think
i want to call you?
I think you're
drinkin' and dialin'.
I can smell the vanilla
stoli from here.
Yell to your sister,
not to me.
A week it's be
en and my poor cousin
still is not havin
g her prosthetic leg.
What the fuck
you want me to do?
Tony, please,
i miss you so much.
Can you co
me over here?
Don't ever
call here again.
Didn't you see my
favorite patient today?
Tomorrow.
How's that going?
Let's not,
richard.
I so wish to christ
you hadn't taken him back.
I took you back.
You think the synergy
escapes me?
You start treating
him, we start seeing
each other again.
Richard, richard.
No, seriously.
If you rea
lly want to know,
he had a rea
l breakthrough
last week.
Break- through what?
Somebody's jaw?
You're right, i'm
wasting my time.
Better i should
boycott with
the national
italian- american
foundation
and save the world from,
uh, what is it this week?
Um...
"gangster"?
The very idea abc would
even think of producing
that stereotypical
goombah- fest.
Richard, we're an
advertisement for the
american experiment.
We did great.
I'm so fed up with people
assuming i'm a thug.
Because my name
ends in a vowel.
Undershirts,
yelling.
Hollywood tries
to give these sociopaths
the tragic grandeur
of al pacino.
You know, he's an
expert at this, jen.
The guy's conning you.
Condescend to
me, richard.
It gets me so hot.
Tell me a little more abou
t this breakthrough then.
You yourself said
the guy's alixithymic.
You said nothing
's gonna get through.
Not if it threatens
that straw house
he's built inside his head
to shelter his
base criminality.
It really concerns m
e you don't see this, jen.
I mean, pink slip
this guy.
He's dangerous.
I'm gonna
pink slip you
if you don't get that
chicken in the oven.
Is that new?
Looks good.
Did you bring
your log?
My log?
Remember
last week?
You were gonna
keep a record.
I asked you to write down
any feelings of anxiety
or memories of past
anxiety attacks.
Yeah, my parents
and the pork store.
I know.
Yeah, that was...
interesting.
Have you thought
at all about that?
How do people
find the time?
To get well?
Look, my mother's dead.
I haven't had
a panic attack since.
You've gone months
without them before.
The conflicts that cause
them and your depression
are buried
deep inside you.
Are you happy?
Am i happy?
That's not even...
look...
i'm sorry i didn't
bring the list.
I'll bring i
t next week.
We oughta think
about bringing your
wife into this.
In here?
Carmela?
You're the one who
wanted to take a more
proactive approach.
That's not
in the future.
Let's talk frankly.
You demanded
more of me.
Fine.
But you're
not trying.
Yeah, i know.
The past.
But shit happens
in my daily life
that needs
attention now.
I've got some
genuine concerns...
about my son.
He shies away from anything
that requires effort
and i think maybe he
picks that up from me.
I mean, he's i
n football now, right,
but carmela's just as
guilty about this as i am,
'cause she indulges him.
Richard was right.
I've been charmed
by a sociopath.
Why didn't i listen?
Why, do you think?
Why did i reject a
good man like richard
in the first place?
If you think about my
life, it's so textbook.
Marry a man
10 years my senior,
of course richard's gonna be
protective and patriarchal.
Then i reject him
for being exactly that.
There's nothing wrong with
wanting to be safe, jen.
It's a bas
ic human need.
I know richard's right.
I should get
tony soprano--
oh, shit.
I always thought
it was that other
guy in the news.
Little augie aprile.
I can't believe
i revealed his name.
Why did you?
Does richard know
who he is?
I think he saw it
in my daytimer once.
That's why he's been
so adamant, because
soprano is very high up.
If he was just some
button man you wouldn't
be treating him?
Elliot, please, huh,
with the terminology?
Jennifer...
you know psychotherapy
is limited
in the treatment
of anxiety disorder.
Now, you've medicated
soprano properly,
you've helped him gain wha
t insight he's able to absorb.
It's time to send
him on to a behaviorist.
Janice!
I was downstairs
cleaning up.
When did you
change the locks?
The minute that ukrain
ian dye job was out the door.
Don't mess with
the russians, janice.
That's all
i'm gonna say.
She can have
her leg back
when she returns
ma's record collection.
And don't say you wouldn't
have done the same thing.
I'm getting calls at
my house from her cousin.
Miss petrograd
carburetor
works of 1987?
I can't have it.
Don't fuck with me
on this, janice.
Give back the leg.
Tony, those records,
they're yours too.
It's sad that
you don't care.
Those old albums...
they're a window
into ma's soul.
In fact, i'm making
a documentary.
The world war ii generation
and their music,
exemplified by ma.
Who the fuck
are you kiddin'?
You're gonna sell them
on the internet.
I have work to do.
Yeah, right,
cleaning up
the cellar.
Good luck finding the lost
dutchman's gold mine, janice.
You'd make more money
working a real job.
Right, like the minute
i'm out of here,
you're not gonna h
ave contractors downstairs
tearing apart
the walls.
Oh, janice...
eh- eh- eh.
You finished?
I want to meet
my bud at the gym,
we're gonna spar.
You got a
girlfriend?
You know who's turning
into a little mink, though?
That meadow soprano.
Look at him
perk up.
I've known her since
we were kids, for chrissake.
Speaking of the royal family
i heard you did a stick- up
with christopher moltisanti.
I wanted to fly down to
south beach, see friends.
My mom wouldn't pay.
Don't worry, i'm not
gonna tell her.
Look, kid...
i'm trying
real hard here.
I know it's
tough on you.
I'm the guy that's
datin' your mom.
Datin'?
Don't get fuck
in' filthy about it.
Anyway, this...
was a good idea she had.
Us going
out to dinner.
Not that i think
one conversation
ever solved
anybody's problems.
I'm only here so i
don't have to hear
her bitching and crying.
The gym, huh?
Mind if i ma
ke a stop first?
My brother- in- law's
out of town.
He said you knew.
I get the bad
tempered one.
Bashir sai
d he told your man
that this month payment
could be late
because we had problems
with the trucks.
Three of them needed
new hydraulics.
Well, nobody
talked to me.
He said yo
u approved.
You're collecting on
my fuckin' routes,
you gotta pay
me a use fee.
They're only your rout
es because you say they are.
You want to question a new
jersey business practice
that goes back 70 years?
Hey!
What is all this,
ralphie?
I oughta stick
a shish kebab
up your ass.
Why do you
provoke me, huh?
This young buck...
he'll fuck your wife
until she moans.
You fucking wop.
You began it, huh?
The fuck you call me?
You bring my wife
into this?
Put it down!
Hey, mister,
come on!
Hey!
Ow!
Get the fucking bat!
You alright,
he get you?
Fuckin' asshole!
School this prick.
In the bread basket.
Good, kid.
Introduce him
to his desk.
You oughta take an
anger management course.
Fuckin' racial slurs.
Why are you doing
this to me?
That's what you
get for using
a baseball bat.
Let's go, kid.
Yeah?
Ginny?
Tony soprano.
Omigod, what's
wrong with me?
I'm a mess here
with the moving.
C'mon in,
i'll get john.
John!
John, get down here,
you got company!
Oh, look who's here.
The guinea
welcome wagon.
This is for yo
u, you piece of shit.
Carmela's bringing
something nice to th
e housewarming for ginny.
They call this
the great room.
I don't see
what's so
great about it.
It's mediocr
e, if you ask me.
We got a fucking
living room right
over there.
I didn't know you were
moving to jersey.
Ginny wanted to be
near her sisters,
and the schools
out here.
We were sitting with
carmine all night long,
you never once
mentioned you boug
ht a place in jersey.
It's not carmine's
favorite subject,
me living in jersey,
but it's what,
half an hour,
40 minutes
over the bridge?
Why didn't you tell
me you were moving here?
Why?
I gotta find out
second hand?
The fuck
do you care?
What do you work
in a toll booth now?
Besides i already
got the condo in
point pleasant.
You should hav
e fuckin' told me.
Ah, tony, i'm
telling you now.
This is strictly
a place for
me to live.
I got no intention of
stickin' my beak in.
I mean, there's our
family and then there's
the soprano family.
Well, don't i ge
t to see the res
t of this shit hole?
Maybe you can help
me unstick this rain bird.
I'm a stranger in
a strange land out here.
Madonn',
look at this pair.
How many napoletans
does it take to screw
in a lightbulb?
There's only candles
in naples right now.
The cardinal of
the church controls
that racket.
That's a
good one.
You like it,
you have can have it.
Use it on
your paesans.
We don't have
those bulb joke,
they don't translate.
Oh.
Tony, i go get
a cappuccino.
Two thousand of
that is mine.
Fuckin' sand monkey
on 17, he's holding
out on us.
So, you treat his
brother- in- law to a
ride in an ambulance.
He said a very
bad word.
Lemme ask you
something.
Why would you take
jackie's kid on
something like that?
Somebody's gotta show him
how the real world works.
Kid's got a chip
on his shoulder,
23- years- old,
he's still
living at home.
So, he can keep an eye
on the pencil prick
that's banging
his mother.
No matter how nice i am
to that little bastard,
he still hates me.
Don't look at me.
I got a daughter
that age.
It's all
a fuckin' mystery.
Amen.
I was thinkin',
being a parent,
that's the hardest job.
It's harder than
this other
shit we do.
The garbage route,
whatever.
Like my first
marriage, my
kid, justin.
Ralphie.
I got some news
you're not gonna like.
I'm putting our friend
in over there as captain.
What?
No, no.
Fuckin' gigi,
are you shitting me?
I'm sorry.
This bullshit
with the arab,
so, i went over the top,
but i'll take care of
it on a people level.
You know this isn't
the first thing.
Well, then at least
tell the truth, ton'.
You want one of your
own people over there
so, he can spy on
the aprile crew.
Yeah.
But i shouldn't
have to.
You got some bad
tendencies, ralphie,
and i sympathize
'cause i got'em too.
But also, you're partnering
up with joe brooklyn
on that shit
at the port.
C'mon, tell me tha
t was a bum decision.
The bottom line
speaks loudest.
I'm earning my
ass off for you.
It's my decision.
Jesus christ, ton'...
i eat dinner
at your house.
This is business.
See?
Turned it off.
Since we last met,
i've been thinking about
your course of therapy.
You're the doctor.
I think you're
ready to move on
to behavior
modification therapy.
What's that mean,
talk to somebody else?
Is this because of
what happened last time?
Look, i'm sorry,
but like you said,
it's hard to think
about that stuff.
It took me how long to
remember it even happened.
I realize that.
You know, you're
fucking unbelievable.
I ask you to get
serious in here,
and when it gets hard,
you pawn me off
on somebody else?
I'm just introducing
the idea.
Something for you
to think about.
I'm going to bring in
some things for you to read
about behavior
modification therapy.
Yes, richard.
He was here
earlier today.
Yes, we talked about
behavior mod. , but--
well, maybe you could.
Listen, i told you i would
discharge him and i will
in my own good time.
Richard, look.
I'm going into the garage,
i'm gonna lose you.
I'll see you later.
Shut up!
Don't turn around.
I said shut up.
I got a knife,
i'll cut you, bitch.
Ah!
Help!
Get off!
Shut up!
I'll give
you all my money!
Shut up, shut up!
No, come on!
I'm gettin
g the panties off.
Stop it!
I'm gonna
fuck you, bitch.
No!
You fucking bitch!
Stop it!
She's almost done, we just
need a few more swabs.
Oh, for godsake, jen.
Richard.
You're alright,
you're gonna be alright.
I thought that i...
i broke my leg,
but it's just really
badly sprained.
Jesus, oh, god.
Bastard.
Did they tell you
that they caught him?
Thank god.
We apprehended somebody
with the description
at a popeye's chicke
n not far from the scene.
Of course, the jer
k is denying it,
but he had
her palm pilot.
Says he found it
on the street.
This is
detective piersol.
She's been great.
There's no way
to describe this.
It's overwhelming.
Of course.
The sonofabitch,
who is he?
Jesus rossi.
Rossi?
Lives over
in elizabeth.
28- years- old,
no priors.
Rossi, that'
s an italian name.
Am i missing
something here?
The girl said he was...
puerto rican
, that's all.
I just want to
take a shower, okay?
We'll be done
here soon.
Alright.
Mom!
Jason.
Jesus, mom.
What did these
lousy fuckers do?
It's okay, i'm
gonna be alright.
I can't believe this
shit, i'm gonna kill
these motherfuckers.
Jason--
fuck it, dad!
The whole worl
d is a fucking sewer!
It's nothing,
but a fucking sewer!
It's a bunch of animal
s out there running wild!
And they're
fucking winning!
Jason, the police caught
the man that did it,
it's okay.
I want five minute
s with that asshole!
Jason, this
isn't helping.
Your mother doesn't need
to hear this, so stop it.
Why don't you go outside
and settle down?
I'll be right out.
Go ahead.
Hello?
Hello, may i speak to
anthony soprano please?
He's not available
to the phone right now.
Whom may i tel
l him is calling?
This is jennifer melfi.
Is this mrs. Soprano?
Yes, it is,
dr. Melfi,
how are you?
Actually, that's why
i'm calling.
I need to cancel
tuesday's appointment.
Oh, he'll be
so disappointed.
Nothing serious,
i hope.
A little car accident,
but i'm fine.
Oh my god.
I hope they
had insurance.
You weren't hurt,
i hope?
Well, my knee got
the worst of it,
but i'll be up and about
in a couple of days.
Well, i'll tell him.
You stay off of it
, you take care.
Who ate the last
piece of cake?
Thank you, i will.
Thank you for
giving him the message.
That's gotta b
e some marriage.
Hello, kate?
This is jennifer melfi.
I know talking on
the phone upsets you,
but i need to canc
el our next appointment.
Tell him what?
That was
your therapist.
Why don't you just
announce it on wfan?
Go find some dust.
She was in
a car accident.
She has to cancel
your next appointment.
She alright?
She said she was okay,
she hurt her knee.
Her knee,
really?
What happened?
I don't know
, she didn't say.
I hope she don't
need stitches.
Stitches on the knee,
they never heal right.
It could leave
a very bad scar.
Any knee injury
can be very serious.
You can get arthritis
for the rest of your life.
Ask joe namath.
No, thanks.
Listen, last time
she mentioned that
maybe you would
come into my therapy...
give your perspective
on the panic attacks
and kind of...
our home life...
whatever.
Sure.
But not no
w, she's sick.
They call yet?
No, not yet.
I would've thought
they'd call by now.
They said they'd call wh
en they want us to come down.
Well...
the hell with it,
i'm gonna call them.
Where's that
detective's card?
They said
they'd call.
I don't wa
nna bother them.
I'm not gonna let
you just wait here.
I'm gonna call them.
Hello, hi,
det. Piersol?
Oh...
i'm on hold.
Oh, she is?
Oh, then maybe
you can help me.
This is
dr. La penna.
I'm calling for
jennifer melfi.
The rape.
Right, det. Piersol
was gonna call
when you were ready
for us to come down
for the line- up.
What, why not?
What's going on?
Well, why?
That's absurd,
that's ridiculous.
Richard,
what happened?
It isn't even piersol.
She's moved
over to juvi.
She never said
anything about that.
So, you just let him g
o, are you fucking crazy?
Yes, i do need to use
this kind of language.
Obviously...
i don't fucking care
if you're sorry.
Richard!
Fine, you do that.
You people haven't
heard the end of this.
I'm contacting
my attorney.
Asshole!
What happened?
They mishandled
the chain of custody,
so, they had to
let him go.
What chain of custody?
They let him go?
Somebody misplaced
the evidence kit
for a little while
or something.
I don't know what
the fuck they did,
those stupid idiots.
Did they just let
him out until the trial,
because i can
identify him.
It's a legal thing.
I think they just
have to let him skip.
That's impossible.
You must h
ave misunderstood.
Gimme the phone.
I want to call them.
I just told you
everything he told me.
Before or after yo
u started cursing at him?
Give me the phone,
i wanna call them back.
Alright, i'll call.
Det. Lindheim,
please?
Yes, i'll hold.
Now, it's not
even the same cop.
Hello, sergeant,
dick la penna again.
I want to apologize for
losing my temper, but--
could i please
have the phone?
Just a second.
Hello?
I'm sorry, i
don't understand
what's going on.
I don't know what you
people did but i
can identify him.
I don't know
what to say.
I'm stunned.
They...
they had t
o let him go
because they fouled up
the chain of custody.
What am i gonna do?
Well, you're gonna have to
have someone escort you
to your car at night.
What's that
supposed to mean?
That's what the rape
counselor woman told me.
Deserted parking garages
are where a huge percentage
of these attacks happen.
You think this
is my fault.
You blame me for w
hat happened, don't you?
How many times did
i tell you to call
the security guard
when you left
work late?
It wasn't late.
This isn't doing
any good, jennifer.
Let me tell
you something.
If i hadn't had be
en on the phone withyou
maybe i would've seen
that guy in the stairwell.
What?
You and your
fucking hard- on
about my patient!
So, it's
my fault now,
you should
've seen your face
when you heard that that
fucking shitbag that rapedme
had an italian name.
What?
I registered surprise.
You were the one
who told the police
he was a puerto rican.
What differenc
e does it make?
Are you so asham
ed of your background
that any misdeed
by an italian
somehow damages
your self esteem?
This is so
misdirected.
The whole fucking world'
s about your self esteem.
Maybe you don't
have enough.
Jennifer, come on.
Oh, fuck you,
richard.
Jen!
So, how was ralphie,
with you over him?
He busts balls.
Cute.
Anyway, he played it
like it was his idea
to make me captain of
the aprile crew.
What else
is he gonna do?
Tony cut o
ff his gazzis.
Very prudently, ton'.
Not that you ain't
gonna hear mor
e about that later.
Most of the conversation
was about johnny sack
moving to jersey
and all that there.
Yeah, ginny sack told
gabriella she needed
a bigger house.
Ginny sacrimoni?
What she needs is
her own zip code.
New jersey's a small
state, she moves in.
She could
tip it over.
I like a woman you can
grab onto something.
You grab onto
ginny sacrimoni,
your fucking hands
will disappear.
She's so fat, he
r blood type is ragu.
She's so fat,
she goes camping,
the bears have to
hide their food.
When ginny hau
ls ass, she's got
ta make two trips.
Two guys could fuck
her at the same time
and still never meet.
Oh, johnny!
Fuck who?
What?
What's so funny?
Nothing, we're just talkin
g about one of the girls.
Is that all
you deadbeats
do over here,
is talk
about cooze?
When we're not
planting potatoes.
Welcome to
the garden state.
You want a drink?
I mean it, you
don't keep up with
current events?
What?
It's all ove
r 1010 wins.
It's right there
in front of you.
You fuckin' illiterates,
turn it up.
That's right, gary.
After years of planning
and delays,
there's finally
good news for newark.
Coming from the ba
nks of the passaic river
where today state
assemblyman,
ronald zellman,
held a press conference to
announce the release of
the first 25 million dollars
in state and federal
matching funds.
25 fuckin' million,
maddon' mia!
The time has come to return
the city of newark
and its waterfro
nt to its past glory.
By the year 2003,
this long- neglected
stretch of riverfront
will be alive with
condominiums, film
studios, and public parks.
A self- perpetuating
revenue base.
The 100 million dollar
newark museum of
science and trucking
will serve to
make this esplanade
the destination attraction
of the tri- state area...
and beyond.
This fuckin'
busted valise.
He's worth every
cent of his cut.
Fuckin' drywall
contracts alone.
Thank you very much.
Jen, can i come in?
I'm sorry.
I'm just so
frustrated.
We both are.
I just wanna go
find that bastard
and kill him w
ith these hands, jen,
and i could,
and i would.
But i can't.
They'd put me
in jail.
That's how messed
up things are.
I know.
You said satriale's
at one.
So, now you know
how it feels.
T, i know why i'm here
and i apologize.
I won't let it
happen again.
Don't step in that,
that's my mother's flowers.
I fuckin' asked you to
watch out for jackie jr.
I specifically said
don't let the kid ge
t involved in this thing.
Now, i gotta hear about
some joint on campus
and jackie's
a part of it.
He only drove.
I said i was sorry.
But lemme tell you something,
t, he was an asset.
He pissed on the car
seats, but he handle
d himself very good.
No cowboy shit,
nothing.
Are you listening to me?
Leave him out of it.
The fuckin' kid
begged me for a taste.
He's the heir apparent.
I don't want him mixed
up in this shit.
I promised
his old man.
Oh.
But it's alright
for me?
I didn't say that.
What else
did you say?
That the life'
s good enough for me,
but not for little
lord fuckpants?
Look, he's not
suited to it.
He's not like you.
Like us.
Kids today,
they're bored,
they're spoiled.
Look, i promised
his old man.
What?
You promis
ed him what?
I don't know.
I was his best friend.
Don't bust my balls.
I gotta go make
a stop in nutley.
Come here.
I love you.
You're a good boy.
"Little lord
fuckpants"?
Whose moniker
is that?
I'm not sure
it is a moniker.
Hi.
C'mon in.
Jesus.
What's the other guy
look like?
Jesus christ, must'v
e been some accident.
What happened?
Oh, someone ran
a stop sign on
eisenhower parkway.
It was just on
e of those things.
I know a woman
with one leg.
Terrible
thing.
Last time we met,
we talked about
getting you into
some behavioral therapy.
I brought a couple of things
for you to look at.
"Feel the fear
and do it anyway".
You gotta be
fuckin' kidding me.
The title leaves
something to be desired--
it's okay,
it's just your...
it's okay, sorry.
Sorry.
You want me to...
it startled me,
that's all.
Maybe you came back
to work too soon.
It's better for me
to be busy.
Right.
I'm okay.
Really.
And i appreciate
your concern.
You see, that's what's wro
ng with the world right there.
An innocent person
is driving along,
minding their own business
and some fuckin' asshole
comes out and
smashes into'em.
You can't control
everything that happens.
But you can
get pissed off.
And then what,
lose control?
Who said anything
about that?
You direct your anger
where it belongs.
You have
panic attacks.
Panic occurs when feelings
of anger, revenge, whatever,
overwhelm you.
That's where behavioral
therapy comes in.
It can teach you to
control those triggers.
Then how do you get people
to do what you want?
You tell your
mother it's hers
anytime she wantsit.
How was your
cousin's shower?
It just sounded like
a bunch of screaming to me.
I was wondering
whose z24 was sitting
in the driveway.
What, did
you get a
new car?
Yeah.
Where did i put the sleeves
for that samovar?
You want anything?
Coke?
No, i'm set, ton'.
I heard about ralph
cifaretto, that he
got passed over.
You heart
about what?
Who?
I'm just saying, ralph,
that was probably
a smart move.
I mean, the more
i get to know him,
he's kind of
a cool guy, but--
this is none of
your fuckin' concern.
You told me you we
re gonna go to college
then i gotta h
ear from chris the shi
t i'm hearing about you?
Oh, you didn't
talk to chris.
Oh, shit.
That's right.
I promised your dad.
Don't make thi
s hard on me, jackie.
I already got one son
to bust my balls.
I'm home!
Ma?
Hey, jackie.
What are you
doing here?
I'm waiting for you.
What, i do
n't get a hello?
I need $200 for
november to put in
my student account.
You don't talk to
me for weeks, but my
money's still green?
I'm looking forward
to total independence,
believe me.
African- americans
go to columbia, dad.
Some of them
are my friends.
Friend, my ass,
under a blanket
on my couch,
watching television
with his shoes
off with you.
Meadow, when did
you get here?
See you later, jackie,
say hello to your mother.
Come into the city,
we'll do sushi.
Don't worry, ton',
i won't say anything
about the mulignan.
You just remember
what we talked about.
I'll have a chicken
avocado wrap, no dressing.
And a coke, please.
One number three,
dressing on the side.
Thanks.
Ah!
Excuse me,
wait a minute.
Let go of me!
Let the fu
ck go of me!
We don't want
continuation.
You give us leg,
and we go.
What leg?
Don't do
this to me!
Don't push me
to edge.
Repent on yourself.
Motherfucker,
do you know i am?
Do you know wh
o my brother is?
Mother what?
What did you say?
Motherfuck--
those records were
all i had to remember
my mother by.
What could they possibly
mean to her?
A few pennies?
Are you people
really so callous?
Fuck you,
you are callous.
Ah!
Oh, my god!
Help me, please!
Ah!
I felt such
a sense of relief.
I felt safe for
the first time
since it happened.
Empowered.
The vending machine.
My guilt for putting
myself in harm's way.
I read about that too.
That honeymooner
in gainesville, florida,
who rocked
a vending machine
and it fell on top o
f him and killed him.
The dog, though...
i don't know.
The forbidden part
of your psyche,
murderous rage.
Yeah, but at first,
i thought he was after me.
The door said "danger".
Actually, no.
It said,"high voltage,
"call n- j- g- e
before digging."
Jersey gas
and electric.
Was richard anywhere
in all this?
No.
Oh, my god.
The dog.
What?
A rottweiler, elliot.
Big head,
massive shoulders.
Direct descendants
of the dog used
by the roman armies
to guard their camps.
I didn't know that.
And digging?
Who do i dig with
and who's dangerous?
Who could i sic on
that sonofabitch
to tear him
to shreds?
Oh.
Lemme tell you
something.
No feeling has ever been
so sweet as to see that pig
beg and plead and
scream for his life.
Because the justice system
is fucked up, elliot.
Richard's got his
attorney looking
into this
at $300 an hour,
but meanwhile that
employee- of- the- month
cocksucker
is back on the street
and who's gonna
stop him, you?
Jennifer...
civilization--
oh, don't worry.
I'm not going to break
the social compact.
But that's not saying there's
not a certain satisfaction
in knowing that i could
have that asshole
squashed like a bug...
if i wanted.
What happened?
Janice.
I can't drive.
And they broke
three ribs.
What did i
tell you, hmm?
I told you not to mess
with those people.
I was supposed to be married
at this point in my life.
Yeah, so?
The man i loved died.
This is all
i fucking need.
Thanks, janice.
What?
What do you mean, what?
They slapped
my sister around.
Oh.
I'm gonna have
to get payback.
It's always something
with you, isn't it?
Every time i hear
your voice on that phone,
i know it's
gonna cost me.
Time, money.
You never do anything
to simplify my life.
I stole a woman's
prosthetic leg, tony.
When did i get
like this?
You really
want to know?
When richie died.
Till that time,
i was functioning
at a very high level.
I think there's on
ly one trajectory for me.
Really?
God.
See what i mean?
All this
soul searching, janice,
it's always
on my fuckin' dime.
I've hit bottom, tony.
But it's odd...
'cause i feel bo
rn again in the lord.
Hmm.
And i pray togod
and i asked him to forgive
svetlana for what she's done.
Janice, we've been
here before.
With vishnu and
richard fuckin' alpert
and the coyote spirit.
And you know what
it always spells?
Trouble...
for the rest of us.
So, put your fuckin'
clothes on.
Seriously, 'cause i gotta
get the fuck out of here.
I give myself
up utterly
and totally to god.
If this is the bottom.
If not...
you can go now.
Billing needs
to see you.
Follow the blue line.
Carmela...
gorgeous
as ever.
My god,
this house.
You already
got one.
Jesus.
Move to jersey,
okay,
but maybe take
a little bit of
a halfway step.
Fuckin' wife of mine.
Gentlemen, wha
t we do in life...
echoes i
n eternity.
He's fucking obsessed
with "gladiator".
C'mon, it's a great
fucking film.
Streng
th and honor.
Scotch...
and soda.
As long as you're on
the way to the bar.
Ball breaker.
J & b,
right, ton'?
T...
what do you think a pl
ace like this set john back?
Who gives a shit?
Fucking landscapin'
alone's gotta be
100, 150 g's.
And to keep
up this lawn.
Property taxes
, and you gotta
pay those.
Taxes.
Why don't they use the
money to fix the godda
mn air traffic controllers?
Fightin' terrorism,
that's what we should do.
How about that fucki
ng stampede in zimbabwe?
Fuckin' soccer game.
No assigned seating,
always a problem.
You're not usi
ng the cane anymore.
I've been...
making my list.
I even...
bought a little
notebook.
Good, that's good.
And i've been thinking abo
your behavioral therapy idea.
Maybe yo
u got a point.
I could use some help
with a few things
and if they can
help me there,
you know,
i should go there.
No.
You sure about that?
Because the last
couple of times,
i've been gettin
g the distinct feeling
that you were
giving me the boot.
Oh!
What's the matter?
Hey, hey
, hey, c'mon.
C'mon, what
did i do?
C'mon, huh?
Hey, hey,
hey, hey.
What, what'd i do,
what's the matter?
Tell me,
Go sit over there.
We'll do this.
Go!
It's just my knee.
It's okay, go on.
What?
I mean, you want t
o say something?
No.
Captions copyright 2001
home box office
a division of time warner
entertainment company, L. P.